





SUMMARY

Software developer since 2010. Excellent front-end skills with Vue.js, React.js, JavaScript, and CSS. Excellent back-end skills with .NET technologies, C#, MVC, SQL, RESTful, Node.js. Excellent leading and mentoring skills with long years of technical and business experience. Visit my **Codepen** and **Github** profiles to check on some of my works in action.

EDUCATION

University (Bachelor's Degree) 10.2004-02.2011 Istanbul Kultur University - (Formal Education) Engineering and Architecture Faculty, Computer Engineering (English) Graduated 2011

SKILLS

Technologies

JavaScript, Vue.js, React.js, Node.js, Express.js, Electron.js, ES6, CSS, SCSS, .NET, C#, MVC, SQL

Competencies

Progressive Web App (PWA), Single Page App (SPA), front-end architecture, Dynamic SQL, TSQL, Design Patterns, Document-Based (JSON) Data Modelling, SOA(Service Oriented Architecture), Windows and Web Services

EXPERIENCE



Huawei Technologies (08.2022- Present)

Currently I am Technical Lead mentoring and leading two development teams in two different projects. As a part of my role I also run technical interviews for candidate evaluations and giving training about js frameworks to team members.



Kafein Technology Solutions - Senior Front-End Developer (09.2020- 08.2022)

I have taken part as a lead front-end developer in several project from workflow and data management to administration portal and document management.



Adesso Turkey - Senior Front-End Developer (01.2019 – 09.2020)

As a part of the software development team in Philip Morris Sabanci, I am responsible of maintenance and development of PMAktif which is a loyalty program for PMI customers, as well as PMTEP administration portal.

CottGroup - Senior Software Engineer (10.2017 – 01.2019)

I was responsible of development and maintaining of the project Informasoft ((https://informasoft.com/en/). The project is a Human Resources Management Platform with organizational network, training plans, payroll management, leave management, competency, and performance managements.

Technix Technology – Software Engineer (08.2016 – 11.2016)

A company that offers software solutions in energy market. I took part in a development team to improve capabilities and maintain the project Sayax.

Argosia Business Solutions - Senior Software Engineer (10.2011 – 08.2016)
I took responsibility of development and implementation of the project www.corcial.com that we founded in 2011. The project is a social b2b platform created for the organizations and professional individuals providing management to online lessons, exams, surveys, staff, tasks, appointments as well as sharing of documents, videos, contents, and business collaboration.

PROJECTS Vocab Master (Personal)

Vocab Master is my personal game project. Users can train themselves on learning and mastering vocabulary and typing.

Built on vocab-master-api which is a Node.js backend api and Electron+React app on the front-end. You can check on details and development coverage in the github pages:

Vocab Master: https://github.com/arsendemirci/vocab-master-mono

>>> Javascript, Electron.js, React.js , Redux, SCSS, Node.js, Express.js, SQLite

AG Watch (Huawei)

<u>AG Watch</u> is an AppGallery health application used to connect any huawei smart watch manage and customize your watch properties and features.

>>>> VueJS, Vuex, JavaScript,SASS

AG QuickApp - Engine (Huawei)

Quickapp engine is a javascript framework similar to VueJS, its used together with QuickApp IDE. Me and my team is responsible for implementing new features to expand the capabilities of the framework

>>>> Quickapp, Javascript, CSS, Karma,

PROJECTS Paperzero.com (Kafein - Eczacibasi)

<u>Paperzero.com</u> is a document management platform with e-sign integration. I was responsible of frontend development of the project from start to end as lead frontend developer.

>>> Javascript, React.js, Redux, CSS, SCSS

Kybele (Kafein - TURKCELL)

Kybele is a workflow and data management project within GDPR. I was the lead front-end developer of the project, where I managed to implement the new requirements.

>>>> Vue.js, Vuex, ES6, Javascript, Vuetify, SASS

PMAktif (Adesso – Philip Morris)

<u>PMAktif</u> was a CRM portal designd and developed as a Progressive Web App used by stores that sells Philip Morriss brand products. I was lead frontend developer responsible of entire frontend development from start to deliver.

>>>> Vue.js, Progressive Web App, Vuex, ES6, SCSS, Javascript

PMTep (Adesso – Philip Morris)

Project is the administration site for the PMAktif project. I took part as a lead full-stack developer to refactor and maintain the project and to implement new requirements.

ASP.NET MVC5, MS SQL, Vue.js, JQuery, WCF, ES6, SCSS, Webpack/Babel

Arcelik Perakende Akademisi (Argosia – Arcelik)

<u>Arcelik Perakende Akademi</u> is a web application for employees to take online courses, access related content, attend surveys and quizzes. I was responsible of frontend development from start to end.

>>>> Vue.js, ES6, SCSS, JavaScript, WebPack/Babel, NPM, ASP.NET MVC5

Informasoft (CottGroup)

<u>Informasoft</u> is a Human Resources Management Platform with organizational network, training plans, payroll management, leave management, competency, and performance managements.

C#, SQL, JavaScript, ES6, Vue.js, WebPack/Babel, NPM, ASP.NET MVC5, Repository Pattern, Unit Of Work, IoC (Unity), Entity Framework Model-First

PROJECTS Corcial (Argosia)

<u>Corcial</u> is an enterprise social network that we founded during my working period in Argosia. It is designed for the organizations and professional individuals providing management to online lessons, exams, surveys, staff, tasks, appointments as well as sharing of documents, videos, contents to provide business collaboration. And it turned into a software as a service, so we customized it to corporates. During that period, I developed and implemented countless modules integrated to the project



C#, WebForms, MS SQL, Custom JSON Document database, ADO.NET, Dependency Injection, Abstract Factory, Javascript, WCF, Ajax, MVVM(JsRender, Observables), Windows Service

Smart Convention Center

A 3D virtual museum game project developed on the Unity3D platform.



Unity3D, MonoDevelop, C#, Singleton Pattern, JavaScript, JSON, LINQ, WCF, Ajax, KnockoutJS

Demo Video:

https://youtu.be/QT6QmHJlb9Y

Fruit Shot

Fruit Shot is a video game that I developed for mobile platform using C# and Unity3D.

Teaser Video:

https://youtu.be/T2GzRQJp438